export const DATA = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which programming language is mainly used for adding interactivity to websites?",
        options: [
            "HTML",
            "CSS",
            "Python",
            "JavaScript"
        ],
        answer: "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is the purpose of a front-end web development framework like React or Angular?",
        options: [
            "To manage databases and server-side logic",
            "To create a visually appealing user interface",
            "To handle server-side routing",
            "To interact with web servers"
        ],
        answer: "To create a visually appealing user interface"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which part of web development is responsible for handling data storage and retrieval?",
        options: [
            "Front-end development",
            "Back-end development",
            "Full-stack development",
            "Middleware development"
        ],
        answer: "Back-end development"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is the primary function of a web server in the context of web development?",
        options: [
            "Rendering web pages on the client's browser",
            "Executing JavaScript code",
            "Storing user data",
            "Handling HTTP requests and serving web pages"
        ],
        answer: "Handling HTTP requests and serving web pages"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which CSS property is used to control the spacing between elements in a layout?",
        options: [
            "padding",
            "margin",
            "spacing",
            "border"
        ],
        answer: "margin"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which of the following programming languages is commonly used for server-side scripting in web development?",
        options: [
            "HTML",
            "CSS",
            "JavaScript",
            "PHP"
        ],
        answer: "PHP"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which of the following is used to read a HTML page and render it?",
        options: [
            "Web server",
            "Web matrix",
            "Web browser",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ],
        answer: "Web browser"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which of the following is a popular front-end framework for building user interfaces in JavaScript?",
        options: [
            "Django",
            "Angular",
            "Flask",
            "Node.js"
        ],
        answer: "Angular"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is DOM?",
        options: [
            "Application programming interface",
            "Hierarchy of objects in ASP.NET",
            "Convention for representing and interacting with objects in html documents",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ],
        answer: "Convention for representing and interacting with objects in html documents"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is the purpose of the event handlers in the JavaScript?",
        options: [
            "Adds innerHTML page to the code",
            "Allows JavaScript code to alter the behaviour of windows",
            "Performs handling of exceptions and occurrences",
            "Change the server location"
        ],
        answer: "Allows JavaScript code to alter the behaviour of windows"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "What is Vue JS?",
        options: [
            "Scripting Language",
            "Framework",
            "Programming Language",
            "Directives"
        ],
        answer: "Framework"
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "What is the purpose of JavaScript in web development?",
        options: [
            "To define the structure and content of web pages",
            "To add interactivity and behavior to web pages",
            "To style and format web pages",
            "To manage server-side data and databases"
        ],
        answer: "To add interactivity and behavior to web pages"
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "Which of the following directives is used to start an angularJS application?",
        options: [
            "ng-app",
            "ng-init",
            "ng-repeat",
            "ng-model"
        ],
        answer: "ng-app"
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "What is React.js?",
        options: [
            "Open-source JavaScript back-end library",
            "JavaScript front-end library to create a database",
            "Free and open-source JavaScript front-end library",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ],
        answer: "Free and open-source JavaScript front-end library"
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "Which of the following is method is not a part of ReactDOM?",
        options: [
            "ReactDOM.hydrate()",
            "ReactDOM.destroy()",
            "ReactDOM.createPortal()",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ],
        answer: "ReactDOM.destroy()"
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "Which of the following is used to pass data to a component from outside in React?",
        options: [
            "props",
            "render with arguments",
            "setState",
            "PropTypes"
        ],
        answer: "props"
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about JavaScript?",
        options: [
            "JavaScript is an Object-Based language",
            "JavaScript is Assembly-language",
            "JavaScript is an Object-Oriented language",
            "JavaScript is a High-level language"
        ],
        answer: "JavaScript is an Object-Based language"
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "Which of the following scoping type does JavaScript use?",
        options: [
            "Sequential",
            "Segmental",
            "Lexical",
            "Literal"
        ],
        answer: "Lexical"
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "Why JavaScript Engine is needed?",
        options: [
            "Both Compiling & Interpreting the JavaScript",
            "Parsing the javascript",
            "Interpreting the JavaScript",
            "Compiling the JavaScript"
        ],
        answer: "Interpreting the JavaScript"
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: "Which function among the following lets to register a function to be invoked repeatedly after a certain time?",
        options: [
            "setTimeout()",
            "setTotaltime()",
            "setInterval()",
            "settime()"
        ],
        answer: "setInterval()"
    }
]